Guide to the David A. Clarke papers, 1974-1997 MS2010
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Part 1 (donated 1990), 1976-1990; Series 1; 82 Linear Feet
  - Subject files, 1976-1990; Series 1 Subseries 1
    - Crispus Attucks Museum and Park of the Arts (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Crispus Attucks Museum and Park of the Arts (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Critique Career Management Services,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Crittenden Street,N.E. 1000 Block- Block Party, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Edna Frazier- Cromwell Scholarship Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - CSX Realty, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Culinary Arts Program, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Cultural Alliance, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - C.U.R.E. (Citizens United for Rehab. of Errants), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Custom Tailor and Design Shop, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - D and W Market, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Dance in the District, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - The Dance Place, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Dard's Parkland Day Care Center, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Datacom Systems Corporation, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Daughters of the American Revolution (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Daughters of the American Revolution (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Davis Memorial Goodwill Industries, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Dawson Earling Learning Center, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Dorothy Day House, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Deafpride,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Dean and Harper Justice Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Death Penalty Defense Fund, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Delaware Baptist Church, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Delaware State Dept. Services for Children, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Delta Airlines,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Delta Sigma Theta Sorority,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Democratic Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Democratic National Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Democratic National Convention (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Democratic National Convention (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Democratic Republic of the Sudan, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committees, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Democratic Socialist Republic of Sri Lanka (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Democratic Socialist Republic of Sri Lanka (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Democratic Socialists of America, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Democratic State Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Democratic State Committee Rally, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Democratic State Legislative Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Dental and Vision Benefits, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Dentistry, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Department of Consumer and Regulatory Affairs Housing, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Department of Corrections, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Department of Education, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Department of Employment Services, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Department of Health and Human Services, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Department of Housing and Community Development, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Department of Housing and Community Development- District Community Development Block Grant, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Department of Housing and Community Development- National Capital Housing Authority, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Department of Housing and Community Development- Redeveloping Land Agency, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Department of Human Services (1 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Department of Human Services (2 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Department of Human Services (3 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Department of Human Services- General Contracting Practices, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Department of Public Works, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Department of Recreation, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Department of State,U.S. Office of Protocol, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Department of Transportation, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Design Forum, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Destination Systems, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Developmental Service Center, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Devon Court Tenants Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Diamond Cab Company, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Dickerson Law School, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Dickson,Jill, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Dillon Computer Consulting, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Dinner Program for Homeless Women, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Diplomatic Immunity, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Directories (1 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Directories (2 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Directories (3 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Disability Focus,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Distinguished Daughters of the Movement, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - District Cablevision,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - District Council Journal, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - District of Columbia Act 7-74, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - District of Columbia Alliance for Preservation, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - District of Columbia Apprenticeship Council, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - District of Columbia Armory Board, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - District of Columbia Art Works, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - District of Columbia Association of Condominiums, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - District of Columbia Association of Deaf Citizens, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - District of Columbia Association of Nurse Anesthetists, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - District of Columbia Association for Retarded Citizens,Inc. (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - District of Columbia Association for Retarded Citizens,Inc. (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - District of Columbia Association of School Librarians, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - District of Columbia Association for Supervision and Curriculum Development, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - District of Columbia Banker's Association (1 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - District of Columbia Banker's Association (2 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - District of Columbia Banker's Association (3 of 3), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - District of Columbia Bar (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - District of Columbia Bar (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - District of Columbia Baseball Commission, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - District of Columbia Black Police Caucus, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - District of Columbia Board of Education, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - District of Columbia Builder's Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - District of Columbia Building Industry Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - District of Columbia Bicycle Advisory Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - District of Columbia Cancer Consortium, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - District of Columbia Center for Independent Living, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - District of Columbia Chamber of Commerce, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - District of Columbia Chapter,American Red Cross, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - District of Columbia Chapter of the National Association of Minority PoliticalWomen, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - District of Columbia City Council, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - District of Columbia Civilian Complaint Review Board, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - District of Columbia Coalition Against the Death Penalty, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - District of Columbia Coalition Against Domestic Violence, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - District of Columbia Coalition for Justice, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - District of Columbia Coalition for Social Work, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - District of Columbia Coalition for Youth, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - District of Columbia Commission on Aging, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - District of Columbia Commission on Judicial Disabilities and Tenure (1 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - District of Columbia Commission On Judicial Disabilities and Tenure (2 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - District of Columbia Commission On Judicial Disabilities and Tenure (3 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - District of Columbia Commission On Judicial Disabilities and Tenure (4 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - District of Columbia Commission for Women, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - District of Columbia Committee on Consumer and Regulatory Affairs, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - District of Columbia Committee to Promote Washington, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - District of Columbia Committee on Public Education, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - District of Columbia COMPAC, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - District of Columbia Congress of Parents and Teachers, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - District of Columbia Consumer Utility Board, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - District of Columbia Contractors' Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - District of Columbia Convention and Visitor's Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - District of Columbia Corporate Volunteer Council, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - District of Columbia Council on Clothing for Kids,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - District of Columbia Council on Family Planning, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - District of Columbia Council 20 AFSCME, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - District of Columbia Court Executive, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - District of Columbia Dakar Capital Cities Friendship Council Incorporated, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - District of Columbia Day Project, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - District of Columbia Democratic State Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - District of Columbia Democratic Women's Club, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - District of Columbia Department of Corrections Furlough (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - District of Columbia Department of Corrections Furlough (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - District of Columbia Department of Employment Services, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - District of Columbia Department of Recreation, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - District of Columbia Dental Hygienist Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - District of Columbia Development Corporation (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - District of Columbia Development Corporation (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - District of Columbia Different Drummers, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - District of Columbia Downtown Partnership (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - District of Columbia Downtown Partnership (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - District of Columbia Employees' One Fund Drive, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - District of Columbia Energy Office, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - District of Columbia Federation of Chapters NARFE, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - District of Columbia Federation of Civic Associations (1 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - District of Columbia Federation of Civic Associations (2 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - District of Columbia Federation of Civic Associations (3 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - District of Columbia Federation of Civic Associations (4 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - District of Columbia Federation of Civic Associations (5 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - District of Columbia Federation of Civic Associations (6 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - District of Columbia Fire Department, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - District of Columbia General Hospital (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - District of Columbia General Hospital (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - District of Columbia General Hospital Commission, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - District of Columbia Government Comprehensive Merit Personnel Act, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - District of Columbia Government Hispanic Employees Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - District of Columbia Habitat for Humanity, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - District of Columbia Home Economics Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - District of Columbia Homeless Coordinating Council, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - District of Columbia Hospital Association (1 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - District of Columbia Hospital Association (2 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - District of Columbia Hospital Association (3 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - District of Columbia Hospital Association (4 of 4), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - District of Columbia Housing Finance Agency, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - District of Columbia Hunger Action, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - District of Columbia Initiative Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - District of Columbia Institute of Mental Health Hygiene, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - District of Columbia Jail Inmates, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - District of Columbia Jewish Community Center, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - District of Columbia Judicial Reorganization Act of 1989, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - District of Columbia Junior Miss Scholarship Program, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - District of Columbia Kenya Exchange, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - District of Columbia Land Title Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - District of Columbia Law 6-125, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - District of Columbia Law Revision Commission, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - District of Columbia Life Underwriter Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - District of Columbia Lottery and Charitable Games Control Board, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - District of Columbia Lung Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - District of Columbia Marathon, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - District of Columbia/Maryland Democratic Socialists of America, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - District of Columbia Medical Society, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - District of Columbia Mental Health Information Act, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - District of Columbia Metropolitan Area Dietetic Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - District of Columbia Music Center, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - District of Columbia Mutual Housing Association,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - District of Columbia National Bank, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - District of Columbia Natural Gas (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - District of Columbia Natural Gas (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - District of Columbia Nuclear Weapons Freeze Advisory Board, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - District of Columbia Nurses Association (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - District of Columbia Nurses Association (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - District of Columbia Occupational Information Coordinating Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - District of Columbia Offices of Community Services, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - District of Columbia Office of Human Rights, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - District of Columbia Office of Human Rights Minority Business (1 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - District of Columbia Office of Human Rights and Minority Business (2 of 2), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - District of Columbia Office of Personnel Employees, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - District of Columbia Office of Public Affairs, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - District of Columbia Parent-Teachers Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - District of Columbia People's Council, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - District of Columbia Political Action Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - District of Columbia Preservation League, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - District of Columbia Prisoner's Legal Services Project, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - District of Columbia Private Industry Council, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - District of Columbia Psychological Association,Inc., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - District of Columbia Public Library, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - District of Columbia Public Opinion Survey of Drug Abuse and Crime, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - District of Columbia Public Schools, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - District of Columbia Public Schools Support Initiative of 1986, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - District of Columbia Public School Teachers, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - District of Columbia Rape Crisis Center, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - District of Columbia Redevelopment Land Agency and Parker Group Ltd., undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - District of Columbia Regional MLK Holiday Committee, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - District of Columbia Reinvestment Alliance, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - District of Columbia Residential,Commercial and Institutional Structure Protection Study Commission, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - District of Columbia Resistance Coalition, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - District of Columbia Retired Teachers Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - District of Columbia Retirement Board, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - District of Columbia School Counselor Association, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - District of Columbia School of Law (1 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - District of Columbia School of Law (2 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - District of Columbia School of Law (3 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - District of Columbia School of Law (4 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - District of Columbia School of Law (5 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - District of Columbia School of Law (6 of 6), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - District of Columbia Self Determination Coalition, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - District of Columbia Services for Independent Living, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - District of Columbia Soccer Council, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - District of Columbia Society for Crippled Children, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - District of Columbia Special Assistant to the Mayor, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - District of Columbia Special Olympics, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 45, Folder 11)